https://www.sextoys.co.uk/terms-and-conditions/

Terms and Conditions – Sex Toys UK
Skip to content
Account details
Search for:
0
No products in the basket.
0
Basket
No products in the basket.
Page Contents
Terms & ConditionsAge of ConsentContract FormationData ProtectionPrivacy PolicyPrice CheckerDeliveryUK Based OrdersDiscount Offers & Voucher CodesWaste Electrical Equipment (WEEE) RegulationsDisclaimerCopyrightAcceptance of Terms & Conditions
Terms & Conditions
Age of Consent
By purchasing products from sextoys.co.uk you declare that you are 18 years of age or above or have the legal right to possess adult products in your area or community. If it is discovered that you are not of the legal age to purchase from the website, sextoys.co.uk is not obliged to accept your order.
Contract Formation
Orders made through sextoys.co.uk are subject to acceptance and availability. Sextoys.co.uk may choose at any time to cancel your order. No contract will officially exist between yourself and sextoys.co.uk until your parcel has been despatched.
Sextoys.co.uk provide a secure checkout for the encrypted delivery of sensitive customer information such as contact and credit card details. Please see our Security page.
Your credit card is charged in the name of our parent company, With A Passion.
Data Protection
Sextoys.co.uk is compliant with the Data Protection Act. Your details will not be passed on to any third party without prior consent.
Privacy Policy
We may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested. We will only use this information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services, it is never sold or passed on without consent.
Our site allows you to opt out of receiving communications from us when we request your information. Also if you want to opt out at a later point, you can do so by e-mailing us or writing to our address.
We use cookies and other technologies only where required for our shopping technology to work. Your personal information will never be stored in any cookies generated by our systems.
Read more about our privacy policy here.
Price Checker
Sextoys.co.uk is happy to price match products found cheaper on alternative sites under the following conditions.
The cheaper product is in stock & available for immediate dispatch.
The alternative web site is not a marketplace or auction site (Amazon, Ebay etc.).
The cheaper product is not listed as a sale or promotion item.
The cheaper product is being sold on a UK based web site.
Delivery
Please note our Christmas Delivery Information for orders over the holiday period
Royal Mail Tracked – £3.95 / 1 – 3 working days – FREE over £30
Interlink Express 24 – Guaranteed Next Working Day – £5.95 / 1 working day – FREE over £60
Europe – Royal Mail Overseas Airmail / Other Courier – £10.00 / 3 – 7 Working Days – FREE over £100
UK Based Orders
Royal Mail Tracked Delivery – Delivery usually within 1 to 3 days. However 10 working days should be allowed before contacting us if your order has not arrived (Royal Mail Terms & Conditions for Royal Mail Tracked)
Interlink Express 24 Guaranteed Next Working Day Service – Guaranteed to arrive Next Working Day Monday to Friday. (With this service you will receive an email and/or text with an estimated hour time slot for delivery. You will also be given the opportunity to re schedule your delivery to suit you!) Deliveries are normally between 9am – 6pm.
International Orders – International orders usually arrive within 3 to 7 working days.
PLEASE NOTE: that if you live in the Highlands area delivery may take longer than specified. Orders outside of mainland UK are unlikely to arrive next working day. Please allow 2-5 working days, depending on the destination. In case of adverse weather please check the Interlink and Royal Mail websites for possible delays.
Discount Offers & Voucher Codes
Sextoys.co.uk has the right to end offers at any time. In the instance that a customer has two or more discount codes they should use the code for the greater amount as discount offers and voucher codes can not be added together.
Waste Electrical Equipment (WEEE) Regulations
Waste Electrical Equipment (WEEE) Regulations state that all electrical equipment – including sex toys – must be disposed of at a designated electrical waste collection centre and not in your regular dustbin. When you buy an electrical item from us, we will dispose of your old one correctly for free. Click here for more details
Disclaimer
All goods sold through this site are sold as ‘novelty goods.’ The vendor, With A Passion Ltd, the holding company of sextoys.co.uk, cannot be held responsible for any injury caused by improper use.
Goods or packaging of goods may differ slightly to those displayed on the website.
With A Passion Ltd, holding company of sextoys.co.uk cannot be held responsible for errors or interruption on the website.
Copyright
Material on this site may not be copied, reproduced, republished, downloaded, posted, broadcast or transmitted in any way without the permission of With A Passion Ltd.
Acceptance of Terms & Conditions
Use of this site constitutes your acceptance of these terms and conditions, which take effect on the date of which you first use the site. These Terms and Conditions do not affect your statutory rights.
Klarna
In cooperation with Klarna Bank AB (publ), Sveavägen 46, 111 34 Stockholm, Sweden, we offer you the following payment options. Payment is to be made to Klarna:
Pay in 3
Pay Later
Further information and Klarna’s user terms you can find here. General information on Klarna can be found here. Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in Klarnas privacy statement.
Sex Toys Blog Categories
anal sex toys (1)
Ask Rebecca (88)
Competitions (6)
Diary Of An Intern (4)
Erotic Art & Design (16)
Good To Know! (173)
Industry Interviews (4)
Kink Corner (49)
Lets Talk About Sex (310)
Love and Romance (65)
Men's Den (48)
Product News (212)
Review Of The Month (9)
Sex News (537)
Sex Tips (150)
SexToys.co.uk News (101)
Special Offers (117)
Survey (2)
Top Picks (103)
Uncategorised (15)
Uncategorized (21)
Vibe TV (9)
Vibrators (5)
Weird & Wonderful (70)
Popular Sex Toy Categories Sex Toys
Sex Toys for Women
Vibrators
Dildos
Love Eggs
Sex Toys for Men
Cock Rings
Fleshlight
SOCIALISE WITH USSubscribe To Our Mailing List
Join the sex toys newsletter to receive 15% off your order and to get all the latest sex toys news, trends and offers straight to your inbox. By entering your email address, you are agreeing to our Terms of service, Privacy Policy, and to receive emails from With A Passion Ltd (sextoys.co.uk).
Why Shop At SexToys.co.uk
Fast, Discreet & Free Delivery
The Best Sex Toys Brands
Passion Points Rewards Scheme
365 Day Returns Policy
Customer Commitment
Help & Advice
Security
How to use a Fleshlight
Are sex toys safe?
How to use a vibrator
How to clean sex toys
How to use kegel balls
Contact Us
0800 1957474
UK FREEPHONE
International: +44 (0)1273 022013
customerservice@sextoys.co.uk
Contact Details & Opening Hours
Klarna
Klarna FAQ
Copyright 2020 © SexToys.co.uk. All Rights Reserved | The UK's leading Sex Toys store
Search for:
Women
Vibrators
Bullet Vibrators
Clitoral Vibrators
Couples Vibrators
G Spot Vibrators
Luxury Vibrators
Magic Wand Vibrators
Log in
Lost your password?
Register
Email address *
Password *
Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our privacy policy.
Register
